antonia.it 2018-11-25

# PRIVACY POLICY - ANTONIA

**PRIVACY POLICY**

The Regulation UE 679/2016 describes how to manage the site in relation to the processing of personal data of users who consult it.   
This notice is given under art. 13 of Reg. UE 679/2016 - in the field of personal data protection to those who interact with the Site and the services offered. The information is provided solely for the Site and not for any other websites accessed via links. 

**-Data Processing**  

Consultation of this site may entail processing data of persons identified or identifiable. The data processor is ANTONIA S.R.L. VIA CUSANI 5  20121, MILANO ITALY .

**-Place of Data Processing**  

The processing of data related to the web services of this website takes place at the offices of ANTONIA S.R.L. and is only handled by technical and specialized staff, or others charged with occasional maintenance operations.   
The personal data provided by users who request informative material (bulletins, CD-ROMs, newsletters, annual reports, answers to questions, etc.) are used only to perform the service requested and are communicated to third parties only where this is necessary for that purpose (shipping services/courier).  
 **-Types of Data**  

The computer systems and software procedures used to operate this website acquire, during their normal operation, some personal data whose transmission is implicit in the communication protocols of the Internet.   
This information is not collected to be associated with identified individuals concerned, but by their very nature could, through processing and association with data held by third parties, allow users to be identified. This category of data includes IP addresses or domain names of computers used by users connecting to the site, URI (Uniform Resource Identifier) of requested resources, time of request, the method used to submit the request to the server, the size of the file obtained in reply, the numerical code indicating the status of the reply given by the server (successful, error, etc..) and other parameters regarding the operating system and computer environment.   
These data are used only to obtain anonymous statistics on site usage and to check its correct functioning and is deleted immediately after processing.   
The data could be used to ascertain responsibility in case of hypothetical computer crimes against the site: except for this possibility, at present, data concerning web contacts do not persist for more than seven days.   
 **-Data provided voluntarily by users**

The optional, explicit and voluntary sending of electronic mail to the addresses indicated on this website entails the subsequent acquisition of the sender, necessary to respond to requests, and of any other personal data included in the message. Specific summary information will be progressively reported or displayed on web pages dedicated to particular services on request.  
 **-Cookies   and** **period for which the personal data will be stored**

No personal data concerning users are acquired by the website. We do not use cookies to transmit information of a personal nature, nor persistent cookies of any kind, or systems for tracking users. 

The use of session cookies (which are not stored permanently on the user's computer and disappear when the browser is closed) is strictly limited to transmitting session identifiers (consisting of random numbers generated by the server) necessary to allow the 'safe and efficient exploration of the site. The session cookies used on this website avoid using other computer techniques that are potentially detrimental to the confidentiality of users' browsing and do not allow acquisition of personal identification data. 

Use of the so-called session cookies – which are not stored permanently on the user's computer and disappear upon closing the browser – is exclusively limited to the transmission of session ID's – consisting of server-generated casual numbers – as necessary to allow secure, effective navigation.

**-Optional Provision of Data**  

Apart from the specified navigation data, the user is free to provide personal data in the request forms to the Guarantor, or those indicated in contacts with the Office, to request the dispatching of informative material or other communications. Their absence can make it impossible to fulfill the request. 

It must be remembered that in some cases (not object of the ordinary administration of this website) the Authority can request information, under CHAPTER VI “Independent supervisory authorities”of the Reg. UE 679/2016, in order to control the processing of personal data. In these cases our reply is obligatory, under penalty of a fine. 

**-Methods of Treatment**  

Personal data are processed by automated tools for the time strictly necessary to achieve the purposes for which they were collected. Specific security measures are observed to prevent the loss of data, illicit or incorrect use and unauthorized access. 

**\- Legal basis for the processing**

The processes are based on the consent of the individuals visiting the web site.  
 **-Rights of Persons Concerned  **

The individuals to whom the personal data refer, have the right at any time to obtain confirmation whether these data exist or not, and to know its content and origin, verify its accuracy or request its integration or updating, or correction (CHAPTER III Rights of the data subject). 

Under this Chapter the Data Subjects have the right to request cancellation, transformation into anonymous form or blocking of the data processed in violation of the law, and to oppose in any case, for legitimate reasons, to their treatment.   
Requests should be sent by e-mail.
